http://www.grandintheatre.com/privacy-policy

Home Box Office
Privacy Policy
The Grandin Theatre Foundation is committed to protecting your privacy. We may collect personally identifiable information when you visit our site. We also collect some non-personally identifiable information for statistical purposes. We do not sell your identifiable information to anyone. When you place an order through our shopping cart, we collect your name and email address to create an account for you. We then redirect you to our secure third-party payment processor, authorize.net, to collect your payment and contact information. We use the information to enhance your visitor experience and to process your order.  Your personal information is accessible only by our staff and server administrator.Your payment information is processed by authorize.net, a secure payment processing service that guarantees the privacy of your information. The security measures we have in place are to protect your personal information.  To safeguard your personal information, we maintain a high level of server security and encrypt account passwords. Your payment and personal information are always safe. The Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software used by our third-party payment processor, authorize.net, is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts your personal information, including credit card number and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet.Our website makes use of cookies, which are small digital files that are stored in your web browser, that enable us to track a logged-in user's return visits to our website. Your browser settings may allow you to block these cookies, but we recommend you have them enabled to help us personalize your experience of our website.
